who could be killed could be sitting at this table right now.
And we're not going to stop, but they need to stop, and they will not stop until they
are stopped.
Thank you.
Thank you, Jack.
I appreciate it very much.
One thing I have to say is that Washington, D.C. was almost as bad, I don't know what
could be worse than Portland.
You don't even have stores anymore.
They don't even put glass up.
They put plywood on their windows.
But most of the retailers have left.
But Washington, D.C. was so bad.
And Pam, I'd say it took 12 days to really make it pretty good, and a month to make it
great.
And now people are going out to dinner.
The restaurants are booming.
They don't have enough seats.
They're opening up new restaurants, because many of them closed.
And people are walking down the street, totally safe.
A reporter, I'm not sure if she's there.
I can't see her.
Somebody report her.
There she is.
She was violently assaulted.
And I don't know, she tends to be somewhat liberal, but she wasn't liberal on this one.
But I appreciated your honesty.
But that won't happen again.
It won't happen again.
You're lucky you're alive, frankly, with what happened.
I know exactly what took place.
So Washington, D.C., our capital, we thought we'd start there appropriately.
And it's safe.
And people are so happy.
They're so happy.
And now it's a couple of months.
I went to dinner there.
I felt totally safe.
I gave a press conference right in the middle of the street, which I don't think Secret
Service was thrilled about.
But I'll tell you what, I wouldn't have wanted to do it six months ago.
It's incredible what happened.
Now we're in Memphis.
As you know, we're having a great impact in Memphis.
It's been only a week.
But it's, Kash, I hear it's been amazing what's happening there, just very early.
But you take a look at D.C. and you take a look at some of the other.
We've had a big impact there.
What we haven't said, because Pritzker said, well, crime is going down in Chicago.
Five months ago, Kash went to Chicago with a lot of FBI agents just to prepare it so
that we went in with, I guess you could call it a surge, call it whatever you want, but
would be even more effective.
And we're going to be doing that and very, very strongly doing that, because Chicago
is a very unsafe city.
It's a great city.
The head of the Union Pacific Railroad said, sir, please, save Chicago.
It can be saved.
Other cities are gone.
I mean, they're lost.
They can get better.
But they're just really they've been so decimated.
But I'm so proud of what they've done so quickly in D.C. and it's taking place quickly in Memphis,
where we were asked to go by the mayor and by the governor.
And it's truly incredible what we can do and how fast we can do it.
Let's go for two more.
Would you like to go and then, Katie, you'll go.
OK, please.
Yeah.
Thank you, Mr. President, for having us here.
And not to sound like a broken record, but it needs to be said that Antifa is real.
It's a threat.
I just saw him last weekend over in Portland while they're causing mayhem over there.
And the reason why there's such a big problem is because we have Democrats and a lot of
people in the mainstream media refusing to acknowledge that they even exist.
Right.
So how can we as a country begin to address it if we have large swaths of, you know, these
people who are supposedly decision makers and people who are supposed to inform?
They don't want to say that it exists.
You know, because the common argument is, well, they're not a real organization because
there's no national leadership.
They don't have a national headquarters.
So how can law enforcement go after a group that doesn't exist like that?
Well, law enforcement goes after criminal groups that organize to rob banks or do smash
and grabs.
They don't have a registered LLC.
They don't have official membership cards.
They don't have, you know, a business address.
But they but law enforcement still goes after them because they're working as a group.
These people don't just show up, you know, randomly at the same time to do the same thing
dressed in a very similar fashion, espousing the same ideology.
And they say, well, it's an ideology.
It's like, well, yes, it's an ideology because there's people alive present that believe
in it and they're acting on it.
And so I've been very well aware of what Antifa has been doing.
I was very busy during the riots in 2020.
That was probably my most exposure to them prior to this year.
You know, I've been I've been at the ICE facility at Broadview.
I'm originally from the Chicagoland area, unfortunately, but that's where I that's where
I grew up around.
Like I said, I was in Portland.
I was covering the riots in Los Angeles as well.
And probably the one of the most disturbing parts about that is in addition to Antifa being
present there, they were tagging the streets with CJNG, which is Cartel Jalisco Nuevo Geronacion,
which is a cartel.
So you have these people who are working basically in concert with other terrorist groups to
say that we're here, we're present, and we're going to we're going to attack federal agents
and people who are going to expose what we do.
And so, to be clear, political violence, sustained political violence that we're seeing in this
country is not a both sides issue.
I was, you know, I was at Charlie Kirk's memorial in Glendale recently, conservative gathering,
totally peaceful.
It was the most peaceful gathering that I've been at.
Every other time that I've been covering violence in the streets, just this year,
just this year, it's always been from left wing people, radical left wing people.
And it's not even just Antifa anymore.
The shooting that happened in, the defensive shooting that happened in the Chicago area,
you know, that wasn't someone dressed in black block.
That was just somebody that had taken upon themselves to go out and try to interfere
and ram federal vehicles.
So people are becoming more and more radicalized, and it was to be expected, unfortunately.
And the reason why we're in this position today is because after I was done covering
the riots, I was at the border from the San Diego sector all the way down to the Rio Grande
Valley sector, covering the border crisis month after month, and we all knew the solution
to that.
We all knew why it was happening.
It's because, well, it's racist to have a border.
It's like, well, actually, it's not, but okay.
And so it required you to come back into office and to fix the problem, but it's no longer
just a border issue.
It's a nationwide issue, and that's one of the reasons why you got elected back into
office, because thankfully the American people said we're not going to deal with it anymore.
But unfortunately, there's a lot of people, as we've seen, who are willing to take to
the streets to do violence.
And that's a scary thing, because typically when I was in 2020, you know, I was covering
Minneapolis, Los Angeles, Portland, Seattle, I was over in Chaz, and that was to be expected.
But now, because the issue of immigration, illegal immigration, is so widespread, riots
can happen anywhere.
Attacks can happen anywhere.
So that's why it was weird kind of going back to my home state to cover this violence.
I mean, just after the Dallas shooting, they were chanting outside Broadview, shoot ICE.
Shoot those F-ers.